Wiktor ZIEJEWSKI

1996





8

(+48) 505 333 789



wiktor.ziejewski@gmail.com



Warsaw, Poland

I started my adventure in an advertising / printing industry - but I felt that this wasn't IT. I've took some time to rethink, and look for something I will be passionate about... and got inspired by my friend - Back-End Developer. I started to diggin in and decided that I want to take a course in Kodilla.com and learn how to become a Front End Developer. I'm at the beginning of my journey and I look for a space where I can grow, learn at polish my skills. I've chosen React as a technology I want to specialise in, but I also want to learn AEM in the future. For now I want to focus on gaining professional experience and team work.

Skills

★★☆☆☆ - HTML, CSS, RWD

★ ☆ ☆ ☆ · React, React Router, Redux, JavaScript

★★☆☆☆ - Jira

★★☆☆☆ -Agile/ SCRUM

★★☆☆☆ - Git, GitBash, GitHub

- Adobe suite

(Photoshop/Illustrator/After Effects)











Education

01/2021 - 06/2021

Front-end course at Kodilla.com school

09/2013 - 06/2017

Technical School No. 24 in Warsaw direction: advertising graphics and multimedia specialization: digital graphic process technician



Experience

09/2020 Ekspresowo

Co-managing with my dad in family company

06/2017 - 08/2017 PrintMedia24

Printing Assistant

- Operation of printing machines
- Conceptualizes and creates covers for books
- Customer service

12/2016 - 05/2017 Addicters advertising agency, Junior Graphic Designer

- Working as part of the Brand team with research and development of creative projects
- Assist in the development and execution of concepts and visual ideas
- Collaborated with design team in creating graphic
- Conceptualizes and creates vector illustrations.

旅

Interpersonal skills

- Involvement
- Accuracy
- Relationship buliding
- Openness and honesty
- Teamwork / Colaboration
- Self motivation



Projects

https://github.com/Wiktor-prog



Certificate

- bootcamp front end